<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Guide For PUBBG MOBILE</string>

    <!--    Homepage-->
    <string name="Attachements">ATTACHEMENTS</string>
    <string name="weapons">WEAPONS</string>
    <string name="ammunitions">AMMUNITIONS</string>
    <string name="throwables">THROWABLES</string>
    <string name="melle">MELLE</string>
    <string name="equipment">EQUIPMENTS</string>
    <string name="consumbales">CONSUMBALES</string>
    <string name="vehicles">VEHICLES</string>

    <!--    Navigation open and close-->
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>


    <!--    attachemenets_homepage-->
    <string name="magazines">MAGAZINES</string>
    <string name="grips">GRIPS</string>
    <string name="scope">SCOPE</string>
    <string name="muzzels">MUZZELS</string>
    <string name="stocks">STOCKS</string>


    <string name="assquickdraw">Assault rifle quickdraw magazine</string>
    <string name="attachableweapons">attachable weapons</string>

    <!--    WEAPONSHOMEPAGE-->
    <string name="assaultrifles">Assault Rifles(AR)</string>
    <string name="sniperrifles">Sniper Rifles(SR)</string>
    <string name="autosniperrifles">Auto sniper Rifles(DMR)</string>
    <string name="submachine">Submachine gun(SMG)</string>
    <string name="lightmachine">Lightmachine gun(LMG)</string>
    <string name="shotguns">Shotguns(SG)</string>
    <string name="pistol">Pistols</string>


    <!--    activity assault rifles-->
    <string name="g36c">G36C</string>
    <string name="mk47">Mk47 Mutant</string>
    <string name="m762">M762</string>
    <string name="qbz">QBZ</string>
    <string name="akm">AkM</string>
    <string name="groza">Groza</string>
    <string name="m16a4">M16A4</string>
    <string name="scarl">SCAR-L</string>
    <string name="m416">M416</string>
    <string name="aug">Aug A3</string>


    <!--    activity sinper rifles-->
    <string name="win94">WIN94</string>
    <string name="awm">AWM</string>
    <string name="m24">M24</string>
    <string name="kar98">kar98</string>
    <string name="mk12">MK12</string>

    <!--    acitivity auto-sinper rifles-->
    <string name="qbu">QBU</string>
    <string name="mini14">MINI14</string>
    <string name="mk14">Mk14</string>
    <string name="slr">SLR</string>
    <string name="vss">VSS</string>
    <string name="sks">SKS</string>

    <!--    acitivity sub-machine-gun (SMG)-->
    <string name="pp19bzon">PP-19 BIZON</string>
    <string name="thompson">THOMPSON</string>
    <string name="uzi">UZI</string>
    <string name="ump">UMP45</string>
    <string name="vector">VECTOR</string>
    <string name="p90">P90</string>
    <string name="mp5k">MP5K</string>

    <!--    light machine gun (LMG)-->
    <string name="m249">M249</string>
    <string name="dp">DP 28</string>

    <!--    shotguns-->
    <string name="s12k">S12K</string>
    <string name="s1897">S1897</string>
    <string name="s686">S686</string>
    <string name="dbs">DBS</string>

    <!--    pistol-->
    <string name="skorpion">Skorpion</string>
    <string name="flaregun">Flare Gun</string>
    <string name="sawedoff">Sawed Off</string>
    <string name="p18c">P18C</string>
    <string name="r45">R45</string>
    <string name="r1895">R1895</string>
    <string name="p1911">P1911</string>
    <string name="p92">P92</string>
    <string name="deserteagle">Desert Eagle</string>


    <!--    Magazinesatachement-->
    <string name="quickdrawextendedmagsrdmr">quickdraw extended mag(sr,dmr)</string>
    <string name="ExtendedMagSRDMR">Extended Mag (SR,DMR)</string>
    <string name="quickdrawMagSRDMR">Quickdraw Mag (SR,DMR)</string>
    <string name="QuickdrawExtendedMagARDMR">Quickdraw Extended Mag (AR,DMR,S12K)</string>
    <string name="ExtendedMagARDMR">Extended Mag (AR,DMR,S12K)</string>
    <string name="QuickdrawMagARDMR">Quickdraw Mag (AR,DMR,S12K)</string>

    <string name="QuickdrawExtendedMagPistols">Quickdraw Extended Mag (Pistols)</string>
    <string name="ExtendedMagPistols">Extended Mag (Pistols)</string>
    <string name="QuickdrawMagPistols">Quickdraw Mag (Pistols)</string>

    <string name="QuickdrawExtendedMagSMG">Quickdraw Extended Mag (SMG)</string>
    <string name="ExtendedMagSMG">Extended Mag (SMG)</string>
    <string name="QuickdrawMagSMG">Quickdraw Mag (SMG)</string>

    <!--    Grips-->
    <string name="lasersight">Laser Sight</string>
    <string name="thumbgrip">Thumb Grip</string>
    <string name="halfgrip">Half Grip</string>
    <string name="lightgrip">Light Grip</string>
    <string name="angledforegrip">Angled ForeGrip</string>
    <string name="verticalforegrip">Vertical ForeGrip</string>

    <!--    Scope-->
    <string name="eightscope">8x Scope</string>
    <string name="sixscope">6x Scope</string>
    <string name="fourscope">4x Scope</string>
    <string name="threescope">3x Scope</string>
    <string name="twoscope">2x Scope</string>
    <string name="Holographicsight">Holographic Sight</string>
    <string name="RedDotSight">Red Dot Sight</string>

    <!--    Muzzle-->
    <string name="PistolsSuppressor">Pistols Suppressor</string>
    <string name="Duckbill">Duckbill</string>
    <string name="Choke">Choke</string>
    <string name="SniperRiflesSuppressor">Sniper Rifles Suppressor</string>
    <string name="SMGSuppressor">SMG Suppressor</string>
    <string name="AssaultRiflesSuppressor">Assault Rifles Suppressor</string>
    <string name="SniperRiflesFlashHider">Sniper Rifles Flash Hiderr</string>
    <string name="SMGFlashHider">SMG Flash Hider</string>
    <string name="AssaultRiflesFlashHider">Assault Rifles Flash Hider</string>
    <string name="SniperRiflesCompensator">Sniper Rifles Compensator</string>
    <string name="SMGCompensator">SMG Compensatorr</string>
    <string name="AssaultRiflesCompensator">Assault Rifles Compensator</string>

    <!--    Stocks-->
    <string name="tactstock">Tact Stock (AR,SMG)</string>
    <string name="bulletloops">Bullet Loops (SR)</string>
    <string name="cheekpad">Cheek Pad (SR,DMR)</string>
    <string name="uzistock">Uzi Stock</string>

    <!--    Ammunitons-->

    <string name="fivesixammo">5.56mm</string>
    <string name="fourfiveammo">.45 ACP</string>
    <string name="sevensixammo">7.62mm</string>
    <string name="nineammo">9mm</string>
    <string name="guageammo">12 Gauge</string>
    <string name="boltammo">Bolt</string>
    <string name="flareammo">Flare</string>
    <string name="magnum">.300 Magnum</string>

    <!--    Ammunitons Describe-->
    <string name="fourfiveammodetail">This .45 ACP round is a Light Bullet type
        with Low Damage Per Seconds but the bullet travels at High Speed at close range.
        Spawning with 15 or 30 bullets in one pack. It can be found anywhere around your loot spots.</string>

    <string name="sevensixammodetail">This 7.62mm round is a Heavy Bullet type with Highest Damage Per Seconds
        but the bullet travel at Medium Speed. Spawning with 15 or 30 bullets in one pack. It can be found anywhere
        around the loot spots.</string>

    <string name="fivesixammodetail">This 5.56mm round is a Medium Bullet type with High Damage Per Seconds and
        the bullet travel at High Speed. Spawning with 30 bullets in one pack. It can be found anywhere around the loot spots.</string>

    <string name="nineammodetail">This 9mm round is a Light Bullet type with Medium Damage Per Seconds but the bullet
        travel at Medium Speed. Spawning with 15 or 30 bullets in one pack. It can be found anywhere around your loot spots.</string>

    <string name="gaugeammodetail">This 12 Gauge round is a Heavy Bullet type with High Damage in Close Range. The Bullet
        Travel Speed is High in Close Range. Spawning with 10 bullets in one pack. You can find it anywhere around your loot spots.</string>

    <string name="magnumammodetail">This .300 Magnum is a Heavy Bullet type with High Damage in any Range. The Bullet Travel
        Speed is High in any range. Spawning with 10 bullets in 1 pack. It can only be found in AirDrop.</string>


    <!--    Weapons-->
    <string name="g36cdetail">G36C - PUBG Mobile. G36C fires 5.56mm rounds and
        has a single-mode as well as full-auto mode. A weapon that can be equipped
        with a variety of attachments and is great for all ranges. G36C is an all-round
        weapon without specific strengths or weaknesses.</string>

    <string name="akmdetail">AKM - PUBG MOBILE. AKM fires 7.62mm rounds and has both a single shot
        and full auto mode. AKM deals a lot of damage in a single shot, but its heavy recoil
        makes it harder to control.</string>

    <string name="mk47detail">Mk47 Mutant - PUBG Mobile. Mk47 Mutant fires 7.62mm rounds with 20 bullets
        per mag. It has both a single shot and double shot modes. Mk47 Mutant is a good medium-range weapon.</string>

    <string name="qbzdetail">QBZ - PUBG MOBILE. QBZ Fires 5.56mm rounds with a single-shot mode and a full-auto mode.
        Stable with low recoil, but slow when reloading and firing speed is not as fast as other 5.56mm rifles.</string>

    <string name="grozadetail">GROZA - PUBG MOBILE. GROZA obtained from airdrops, fires 7.62mm rounds and has both a single
        shot and a full auto mode. Deals a lot of damage in a single shot with a high rate of fire. It is the best
        mid-to-close-range automatic rifle.</string>

    <string name="m16a4detail">M16A4 - PUBG MOBILE. M16A4 Fires 5.56mm rounds and has both a single shot and a burst mode,
        which is very fast and deals high damage in close range. But it does not have a full auto mode, and the burst mode
        is difficult to master.</string>

    <string name="scarldetail">SCAR-L - PUBG MOBILE fires 5.56mm rounds and has both a single and a full auto mode. Light
        recoil, stability, and accuracy make this weapon easier to master. Its rate of fire is lower than other 5.56mm rifles.
        But a fine weapon nonetheless.</string>

    <string name="m416detail">M416 - PUBG MOBILE. M416 Fires 5.56mm rounds with 30 bullets per Mag. It has both a single shot
        and a full auto mode. It can be equipped with lots of attachments to become an all-rounder at any distance.</string>

    <string name="augdetail">AUG A3 - PUBG Mobile. Obtained from airdrops. Fire 5.56mm and has both a single short and a full
        auto mode. With light recoil and great performance in the mid-to-far range. it doesn\'t have any visible weakness.</string>

    <!--    Sniper Rifles Details-->

    <string name="win94detail">Win94 - PUBG MOBILE. Win94 fires .45rounds. Very powerful and fast, but cannot equipped with any scope.
    </string>

    <string name="awmdetail">AWM - PUBG MOBILE. Obtained from airdrops. It is the most powerful bolt sniper rifle and fires unique
        magnum rounds. Deals extremely high damage and ignores rank 3 headgear in long distance.
    </string>

    <string name="m24detail">M24 - PUBG MOBILE. M24 is a great bolt action sniper rifle that fires 7.62mm rounds.
        Second only to the AWM and can eliminate players in Lv.2 headgear with one shot. Relies heavily on scopes and skills.</string>

    <string name="kar98detail">Kar98K - PUBG MOBILE. This single bolt sniper rifle fire 7.62mm rounds that can one-short players
        in rank 2 headgear. Relies heavily on scope and skills.</string>

    <string name="mk12detail">PUBG Mobile 0.19.0 update has been released with a lot of cool features. Apart from the mind-blowing PUBG Mobile
        Livik map which unfold the chaotics world with more enemies and less time, the new updated version of PUBG Mobile also offers
        players with staggering weapons and the MK12 is no doubt the most special one.</string>

    <!--    AutoSniperRifles-->

    <string name="qbudetail">QBU - PUBG MOBILE. QBU is a modern semi-automatic rifle that fires 5.56mm rounds.
        Each shot deals high damage but the recoil is strong. Overall excellent rifle</string>

    <string name="mini14detail">QBU - PUBG MOBILE. QBU is a modern semi-automatic rifle that fires 5.56mm rounds.
        Each shot deals high damage but the recoil is strong. Overall excellent rifle</string>

    <string name="mk14detail">Mk14 - PUBG MOBILE. Mk14 fires 7.62mm rounds with 10 bullets per mag. Obtained from
        airdrops only. Mk14 has light recoil when in single firing while prone, but heavy recoil when in full auto mode.</string>

    <string name="slrdetail">SLR - PUBG Mobile. A Semi-automatic marksman rifle that fires 7.62mm rounds. Powerful
        recoil but deals a significant amount of damage. It requires some skills when firing continuously</string>

    <string name="vssdetail">VSS - PUBG MOBILE. VSS fires 9mm rounds and comes with a suppressor and a 4x scope.
        Light recoil but also less powerful. Difficult to hit moving targets that are far away due to slow initial
        speed and high bullet drop.</string>

    <string name="sksdetail">SKS - PUBG MOBILE. SKS fires 7.62mm rounds. Single shots deal very high damage and
        can be equipped with a variety of attachments.It has heavy recoil and is harder to control when firing continuously.</string>

    <!--    SMG bizon-->
    <string name="bizondetail">PP-19 or Bizon is a new submachine gun in PUBG Mobile version 0.13.5.
        This weapon fires 9mm ammunition and can only be found in Erangel and Vikendi. PP-19 Bizon can be
        equipped with scopes from Red Dot Sight to 6x Scope and all muzzle accessories available for submachine guns. </string>

    <string name="thompsondetail">Thompson SMG fires  .45ACP rounds with 30 bullets per mag.You can obtain this weapon from Ground Loots.
            Thompson SMG has single shot and full auto mode.Thompson SMG deals more damage than other SMGs </string>


    <string name="uzidetail">UZI has single shot and full auto mode. UZI is a very mobile and fast weapon to use in early close combat,
        it is really good against enemies with no protection item, but never underestimate a UZI because sometimes it can come in
        handy. Unfortunately, UZI cannot be equipped with any scope.</string>

    <string name="umpdetail">UMP45 has single shot, double shot, and full auto mode. UMP45 is really good in close range combat.
        It has a high fire rate and very mobile. UMP9 requires lots of attachments so that it can be handled even better. </string>

    <string name="vectordetail">Vector has single shot, double shot, and full auto mode. Vector is a fast, stable and mobile weapon
        it is really good in close range because of fast firing speed but with only 13 bullets it is pretty hard to secure a kill,
        an smg extended magazine is a must for Vector. </string>

    <string name="p90detail">The P90 is an excellent close combat weapon and is a good option for those who like the high fire rate
        of weapons such as the micro Uzi. The ideal way to use the weapon is in the close quarters.</string>

    <string name="mp5kdetail">The Mk12 is a gun which falls in the DMR category. It uses 5.56 ammunition and has a large magazine
        for a DMR. The gun has one of the lowest recoils in the game and feels incredibly smooth when firing. </string>

    <!--    LightMachineGun-->

    <string name="m249detail">M249 only has a full auto mode. M249 is a light machine gun that has the most bullets per magazine,
        with this advantage this weapon is preferred to use against moving a vehicle or providing cover for a teammate, with that
        said M249 is also a range adaptive weapons that can attach scope from red dot sight to 6x. No attachment is required for this
        weapon. </string>

    <string name="dpdetail">DP 28 only has a full auto mode.DP 28 is a light machine gun that has a large magazine able to put over
        40 bullets, the weapon doesn\'t require any attachment beside scopes. It is an adaptive weapon that can shoot at any range
        from red dot sight to 6x scope. </string>


    <!--    Shotguns-->

    <string name="s12kdetail">S12K is a semi-automatic shotgun that able to fires shot continuously and also capable of equipping
        attachment due to heavy recoil and loud sound of fire. It is recommended to use in close range in other to get a good
        amount of damage to an enemy. </string>

    <string name="s1897kdetail">S1897 is a shotgun that deals high damage in close range but doesn\'t fire very fast and took
        a longer time to reload. It is a good weapon to pick up in early landing.</string>

    <string name="s686kdetail">S686 is a double barrel shotgun that can be fired a quick double shot, deals high damage in
        close range, didn\'t really work out in another range. An early game weapon to choose when there are no other weapons
        around you.</string>

    <string name="dbsdetail"> It is a double-barreled pump-action shotgun. DBS is a
        nine-pellet gun and has a base damage of 26. The weapon can fire a massive burst of bullets in a short
        duration. This gun uses a 12-gauge ammunition and has a magazine size of 14. </string>

    <!--    Pistol-->

    <string name="skorpion0detail">Skorpion is a machine pistol that has an ability to fires both single and full-auto.
        The recoil is light and can attach with Scope, Foregrip, Magazine, and Stock to hit a more accurate shot.</string>

    <string name="flaregundetail">Flare Gun is very rare it deals no damage. This weapon requires to fires up towards the
        sky in other to call a special airdrop or armored UAZ when you are outside the safe zone. There are no real stats
        that let you know where to find it exactly. It depends on your luck 100%.</string>

    <string name="sawedoffdetail">Sawed-off is a shotgun pistol that fires 2 bullets per mag, deal very high damage in close range.</string>

    <string name="p18cdetail">P18C is an automatic pistol that has the single and full auto fire more. P18C is a good close range
        pistol that has a fast fire rate but low damage.</string>

    <string name="r45detail">R45 is a powerful revolver that deals with very high damage and very accurate in the close range also
        with fast reload. </string>

    <string name="p92detail">P92 is a semi-automatic pistol that you can easily find in the game when you drop down the parachute,
        it is commonly used for early combat like really early, it works great when holding enemies in close range and when pushing
        enemies with no vest or helmet. To make P92 a good pistol choice you might need to attach some attachment. </string>

    <string name="p1991detail">P1911 is a semi-automatic pistol that has more power when shooting and adapting to a longer range
        and is much more accurate than the other pistol. To get P1911 to reach its precise point you might need to attach some
        attachment for it.</string>

    <string name="DesertEagledetail">The semi-automatic pistol offers massive damage of 62 and two shots on the head is enough to do
        the job. No matter, which helmet you are wearing, it will smash your head down. The effective Fire Range being 100m gives
        a clear message to the enemies to maintain a safe distance or not to indulge in a close combat battle in PUBG mobile game.</string>

    <string name="r1a95detail">R1895 is a very powerful pistol that deals high damage, but the recoil is heavy and this weapon
        can\'t attach Scope, Foregrip, and Mag. It requires a good aim to hit an accurate shot.</string>


    <!--    Weapons Specification-->
    <string name="weapontype">Weapon Type</string>
    <string name="power">Base Damange</string>
    <string name="range">Range</string>
    <string name="recoil">Recoil</string>
    <string name="firingSpeed">Firing Speed</string>
    <string name="firerate">Fire Rate</string>
    <string name="aamotype">Ammo Type</string>
    <string name="magcapacity">Magazine Capacity</string>
    <string name="timetokill">Time To Kill</string>
    <string name="firingmode">Firing Mode</string>
    <string name="availability">Availability</string>

    <string name="reloadtime">Reload Time</string>


    <string name="compatibleattachements">Best Attachments</string>


</resources>

